<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Email_Letterhead</letterhead>
    <name>IOP – 20% off (FY14) – Monthly (ProAdvisor)</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>Your Intuit Online Payroll Subscription</subject>
    <textOnly>Special Offer:
Intuit Online Payroll

Dear {!BLANKVALUE(Contact.Name, &quot;Valued Customer&quot;)}



Thank you for taking the time to discuss your payroll needs with me. I m happy to have been able to introduce you to Intuit Online Payroll, and I hope that I provided you with valuable information.

Intuit Online Payroll is an excellent choice for managing your payroll needs. The service is easy to use, allowing you to create paychecks in minutes. The pricing includes direct deposit, unlimited payroll runs, support, and electronic tax payments and filings. In addition, Intuit Online Payroll has easy download to QuickBooks and other accounting programs.

As I mentioned in our conversation, we are pleased to make a special offer available to you. To sign up for Intuit Online Payroll and receive 1 month FREE plus 12 months at 20% off*, please click here.

If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us.

Regards,






Intuit, Inc., Customer Communications 2800 E. Commerce Center Place, Tucson, AZ 85706.

IMPORTANT NOTICE: Intuit respects the personal nature of email and this email is being sent at your verbal request. A previously stated opt out does not apply to this email. If you would like to update your contact preferences, you may do so at this location.

*Your Intuit Online Payroll 30 day free trial period begins when you run your first payroll. A valid credit card is required. After your trial, you will receive a 20% discount on your monthly service fees for twelve months of your subscription to Intuit Online Payroll. After the 12 months, you will be automatically charged at the then-current fee for the service(s) you ve selected, unless you cancel. Currently the monthly pricing is $35 for Enhanced; or $25 for Basic; or $20 for Household. Each employee you pay is an additional $2.00/month. Pay up to 150 employees. Intuit Online Payroll Enhanced includes 1 state. If you file taxes in more than one state, each additional state is currently $12/month. Intuit Online Payroll Basic does not include tax forms. Sales tax may be applied where applicable. The trial is available for Enhanced, Basic or Household versions. You may cancel at any time online within your payroll account (click the Setup tab then click Cancel Service) or by calling 1-866-729-2925. This limited time offer is valid for new Intuit Online Payroll subscribers only and cannot be combined with other offers. Terms, conditions, pricing, features, service and support are subject to change without notice.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
